<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Dringhouses Primary School</title>
    <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Dringhouses Primary School</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 18:21:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 18:21:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We take your privacy very seriously.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of this we want to provide you with explicit information on how we collect, gather, and identify information during your visit to our site. This information may be expanded or be updated as we change or develop our site. For this reason, we recommend that you review this policy from time-to-time to see if anything has changed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At present we collect information on our users in three ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;by examination of the log files that all visitors involuntarily leave when they visit any web content - this provides a limited amount of information though cannot identify the individual concerned;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;voluntary submission when a question is requested via the Contact Form;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;automatic collection of non-personal information and data through the use of Cookies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The information collected is used to improve the content of the site, thus making your user experience more valuable. This information is NOT being shared with other organisations for marketing purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cookies are small text files a web site uses to recognise repeat users, facilitate the any ongoing access to the site and facilitate the use of the site. Cookies also allow a site to track usage behaviour and compile site usage information that will allow for the improvement of content.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 18:18:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;gill-williams&#34;&gt;Gill Williams&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Head Teacher&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;about_headteacher.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;headteacher welcome&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We hope this website helps you gain an understanding of how our school is organised and gives you a flavour of the exciting opportunities on offer at Dringhouses Primary School.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With its friendly, caring atmosphere it is often described by the community as a &amp;lsquo;village school in York&amp;rsquo;. The children, parents, staff, governors and community are committed to working together to ensure the continuing success of the school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a team we strive to ensure that every child enjoys learning, feels proud of what they can do, and is confident that they can learn new skills and achieve their very best. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already visited, then please come and see the school in action. We would be delighted to meet you and feel sure that you would enjoy your visit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;address&#34;&gt;Address&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dringhouses Primary School, St Helen&amp;rsquo;s Road, York, YO24 1HW&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>